A Guide to the Commonwealth Fund records, Division of Publications, SG 1, Series 13 FA285
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Authors, 2
  - Shands, Harley C. - "The War with Words: Structure and Transcendence" [Grant-in-Aid], September 3, 1964-April 25, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 144)
  - Shands, Harley C. - "The War with Words: Structure and Transcendence" [Grant-in-Aid], September 3, 1964-April 25, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 145)
  - Shands, Harley C. - "The War with Words: Structure and Transcendence" [Grant-in-Aid], September 3, 1964-April 25, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 146)
  - Shannon, James A. - "The Institutionalization of the Biomedical Sciences", August 22, 1973-March 28, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 147)
  - Shapiro, Robert and Franklin Robinson - "The Embroyogenesis of the Human Skull" [Grant-in-Aid], April 10, 1967-July 2, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 148)
  - Shirley, Hale F. - "Children and Society" [Grant-in-Aid], May 23, 1969-January 15, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 149)
  - Sidman, Richard - "Atlas of the Mouse Brain", August 20, 1965-April 6, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 150)
  - Silver, George A. - "A Cry of Children: Social Policy and Child Health: A Cross-Nation Perspective", January 13, 1976-October 11, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 151)
  - Sloane, R. Bruce - "Behavior Therapy and Psychotherapy", October 19, 1970-September 25, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 152)
  - Sloane, R. Bruce - "Behavior Therapy and Psychotherapy", October 4, 1972-May 9, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 153)
  - Society for Health and Human Values - "Changing Roles and Education of Health Care Personnel Worldwide in View of the Increase of Basic Health Services", December 9, 1977-April 17, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 154)
  - Squire, Lucy F. - "Fundamentals of Roentgenology", March 24, 1966-September 30, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 155)
  - Stevens, Rosemary A. - "Specialization in Medicine: A Comparative Study of Britain and the United States", July 2, 1970-March 30, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 156)
  - Strickland, Stephen P. - "Medical Research in the U.S., 1950-1970: A Case Study in National Policy Development", August 25, 1969-March 23, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 157)
  - Strickland, Stephen P. - "Medical Research in the U.S., 1950-1970: A Case Study in National Policy Development", August 25, 1969-March 23, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 158)
  - Strickland, Stephen P. - "Medical Research in the U.S., 1950-1970: A Case Study in National Policy Development", August 25, 1969-March 23, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 159)
  - Stryer, Lubert - "Biochemestry", February 26, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 160)
  - Stryer, Lubert - "Biochemestry", February 26, 1971-April 11, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 161)
  - Telford, Ira R. - "Experimental Muscular Dystrophies" [Grant-in-Aid], October 29, 1965-March 4, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 162)
  - Tennessee Public Health Association - "Tennessee Public Health 1877-1977", July 7, 1977-February 27, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 163)
  - Valverde-Garcia, Facundo - "Studies of the Pirform Lobe", January 8, 1964-December 21, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 164)
  - Walford, Roy L. - "Immunologic Theory of Aging" [Grant-in-Aid], July 1, 1968-April 17, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 165)
  - University of Washington - "Proceedings of 8th International Symposium on Neuroradiology", October 7, 1967-March 26, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 166)
  - Watson, W. Alan J. - "Justinian's Digest", June 8, 1978-January 27, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 167)
  - Watson, W. Alan J. - "Justinian's Digest", June 8, 1978-January 27, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 168)
  - Watson, W. Alan J. - "Justinian's Digest", June 8, 1978-January 27, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 169)
  - Weiner, Herbert - "Critical Studies in Psychosomatic Medicine" [Grant-in-Aid], July 16, 1971-December 21, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 170)
  - Weiner, Herbert - "Critical Studies in Psychosomatic Medicine" [Grant-in-Aid], December 31, 1972-September 24, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 171)
  - White, Kerr and Robert Kohns - "Health Care: An International Study", October 4, 1974-January 15, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 172)
  - Willard, Harold N. - "Care of Chronically Ill Patients Continuing Care in a Community Hospital", December 20, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 173)
  - Williamson, John W. - "Medical Care Outcomes, Assessment and Improvement", Decenber 19, 1975-January 10, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 174)
- Book Program, 3
  This subseries is divided into three sections: Books Received, No Books Received, and Miscellaneous. The sections Books Received and No Books Received are arranged alphabetically by author. The Miscellaneous section is arranged alphabetically.
  The first two sections of this subseries consist of correspondence and financial papers. The Books Received section is concerned with receiving certain books from authors, while the No Books Received section is concerned with the opposite. The various manuscripts of "Patterns of Human Growth" by Edith Boyd are located in the Books Received section. The third section, Miscellaneous, consists of the papers of directors, consultants, and publishing companies. The subseries dates from the late 1960s to the early 1980s.
  - Books Received - Ackerman, Bruce A. - "Beyond the New Deal: A Study in Coal and the Clean Air Act", May 20, 1980-January 14, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 175)
  - Books Received - Ackerman, Bruce A. - "Beyond the New Deal: A Study in Coal and the Clean Air Act", May 20, 1980-January 14, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 176)
  - Books Received - American College of Physicians - "Annals of Internal Medicine: Selection and Interpretation of Diagnostic Tests and Procedures", July 3, 1980-January 29, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 177)
  - Books Received - American College of Physicians - "Annals of Internal Medicine: Selection and Interpretation of Diagnostic Tests and Procedures", July 3, 1980-January 29, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 178)
  - Books Received - Arbona, Guillermo - "Family Planning in Puerto Rico: A Historical Analysis", November 15, 1977-December 8, 1983 (Box 18, Folder 179)
  - Books Received - Barchas, Jack and Jean Renson - "Neuroregulatory Agents, Psychoactive Drugs, and Behavior", May 27, 1971-March 27, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 180)
  - Books Received - Barchas, Jack and Jean Renson - "Neuroregulatory Agents, Psychoactive Drugs, and Behavior", May 27, 1971-March 27, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 181)
  - Books Received - Boyd, Edith - "Patterns of Human Growth", September 3, 1958-December 30, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 182)
  - Books Received - Boyd, Edith - "Patterns of Human Growth", January 6, 1966-February 20, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 183)
  - Books Received - Boyd, Edith - "Patterns of Human Growth", January 6, 1966-February 20, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 184)
  - Books Received - Boyd, Edith - "Patterns of Human Growth", January 6, 1966-February 20, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 185)
  - Books Received - Boyd, Edith - "Patterns of Human Growth" (Editorial Work: Volume I), February 19, 1957-December 1, 1961 (Box 19, Folder 186)
  - Books Received - Boyd, Edith - "Patterns of Human Growth" (Iconometrographic Analysis: Volume II), October 2, 1952 (Box 19, Folder 187)
  - Books Received - Boyd, Edith - "Patterns of Human Growth" (Introduction), December 21, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 188)
  - Books Received - Boyd, Edith - "Patterns of Human Growth" (Manuscript I), March 2, 1961 (Box 19, Folder 189)
  - Books Received - Boyd, Edith - "Patterns of Human Growth" (Manuscript I), March 2, 1961 (Box 19, Folder 190)
  - Books Received - Boyd, Edith - "Patterns of Human Growth" (Manuscript I), March 2, 1961 (Box 20, Folder 191)
  - Books Received - Boyd, Edith - "Patterns of Human Growth" (Manuscript I), March 2, 1961 (Box 20, Folder 192)
  - Books Received - Boyd, Edith - "Patterns of Human Growth" (Manuscript I), March 2, 1961 (Box 20, Folder 193)
  - Books Received - Boyd, Edith - "Patterns of Human Growth" (Manuscript I), March 2, 1961 (Box 20, Folder 194)
  - Books Received - Boyd, Edith - "Patterns of Human Growth" (Manuscript I), March 2, 1961 (Box 20, Folder 195)
  - Books Received - Boyd, Edith - "Patterns of Human Growth" (Manuscript I), March 2, 1961 (Box 20, Folder 196)
  - Books Received - Boyd, Edith - "Patterns of Human Growth" (Manuscript I), March 2, 1961 (Box 20, Folder 197)
  - Books Received - Boyd, Edith - "Patterns of Human Growth" (Manuscript II), April 1970 (Box 20, Folder 198)
  - Books Received - Boyd, Edith - "Patterns of Human Growth" (Manuscript II), April 1970 (Box 21, Folder 199)
  - Books Received - Boyd, Edith - "Patterns of Human Growth" (Manuscript II), April 1970 (Box 21, Folder 200)
  - Books Received - Boyd, Edith - "Patterns of Human Growth" (Manuscript II), April 1970 (Box 21, Folder 201)
  - Books Received - Boyd, Edith - "Patterns of Human Growth" (Manuscript II), April 1970 (Box 21, Folder 202)
  - Books Received - Boyd, Edith - "Patterns of Human Growth" (Manuscript II), April 1970 (Box 21, Folder 203)
  - Books Received - Boyd, Edith - "Patterns of Human Growth" (Manuscript II), April 1970 (Box 21, Folder 204)
  - Books Received - Boyd, Edith - "Patterns of Human Growth" (Manuscript II), April 1970 (Box 21, Folder 205)
  - Books Received - Boyd, Edith - "Patterns of Human Growth" (Manuscript III), March 1972-March 1973 (Box 22, Folder 206)
  - Books Received - Boyd, Edith - "Patterns of Human Growth" (Manuscript III), March 1972-March 1973 (Box 22, Folder 207)
  - Books Received - Boyd, Edith - "Patterns of Human Growth" (Manuscript III), March 1972-March 1973 (Box 22, Folder 208)
  - Books Received - Boyd, Edith - "Patterns of Human Growth" (Manuscript III), March 1972-March 1973 (Box 22, Folder 209)
  - Books Received - Boyd, Edith - "Patterns of Human Growth" (Manuscript III), March 1972-March 1973 (Box 22, Folder 210)
  - Books Received - Boyd, Edith - "Patterns of Human Growth" (Manuscript III), March 1972-March 1973 (Box 22, Folder 211)
  - Books Received - Boyd, Edith - "Patterns of Human Growth" (Manuscript III), March 1972-March 1973 (Box 22, Folder 212)
  - Books Received - Boyd, Edith - "Patterns of Human Growth" (Manuscript III), March 1973 (Box 23, Folder 213)
  - Books Received - Boyd, Edith - "Patterns of Human Growth" (Manuscript III), March 1973 (Box 23, Folder 214)
  - Books Received - Boyd, Edith - "Patterns of Human Growth" (Manuscript III), March 1973 (Box 23, Folder 215)
  - Books Received - Boyd, Edith - "Patterns of Human Growth" (Manuscript III), March 1973 (Box 23, Folder 216)
  - Books Received - Boyd, Edith - "Patterns of Human Growth" (Manuscript III), March 1973 (Box 23, Folder 217)
  - Books Received - Boyd, Edith - "Patterns of Human Growth" (Manuscript III), March 1973 (Box 23, Folder 218)
  - Books Received - Boyd, Edith - "Patterns of Human Growth" (Manuscript III), March 1973 (Box 24, Folder 219)
  - Books Received - Boyd, Edith - "Patterns of Human Growth" (Manuscript IV), December 1974-August 1976 (Box 24, Folder 220)
  - Books Received - Boyd, Edith - "Patterns of Human Growth" (Manuscript IV), December 1974-August 1976 (Box 24, Folder 221)
  - Books Received - Boyd, Edith - "Patterns of Human Growth" (Manuscript IV), December 1974-August 1976 (Box 24, Folder 222)
  - Books Received - Boyd, Edith - "Patterns of Human Growth" (Manuscript IV), December 1974-August 1976 (Box 24, Folder 223)
  - Books Received - Boyd, Edith - "Patterns of Human Growth" (Manuscript IV), December 1974-August 1976 (Box 24, Folder 224)
  - Books Received - Boyd, Edith - "Patterns of Human Growth" (Outline of Chapters: Volume I), October 17, 1960-December 6, 1960 (Box 24, Folder 225)
  - Books Received - Boyd, Edith - "Patterns of Human Growth" (Permission for Illustrations: Volume I and Volume II), April 6, 1961-July 7, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 226)
  - Books Received - Boyd, Edith - "Patterns of Human Growth" (Publishing: Volume I), September 16, 1959-December 10, 1962 (Box 24, Folder 227)
  - Books Received - Brody, Eugene B. - "Contraceptive Behavior in a Developing Country", December 3, 1973-December 23, 1981 (Box 25, Folder 228)
  - Books Received - Cockshott, W. Peter and Howard Middlemiss - "Clinical Radiology in the Tropics", January 18, 1977-February 26, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 229)
  - Books Received - Darby, John Kenneth, Jr. - "Speech Evaluation in Medicine", November 25, 1977-September 22, 1981 (Box 25, Folder 230)
  - Books Received - Finland, Maxwell - "History of the Harvard Medical Unit of the Boston City Hospital", July 21, 1977-March 17, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 231)
  - Books Received - Harris, John W. - "The Red Cell" [Grant-in-Aid], September 1, 1967-April 15, 1976 (Box 25, Folder 232)
  - Books Received - Jason, Hilliard - "Teachers and Teaching in U.S. Medical Schools" [Grant-in-Aid], July 23, 1969-February 28, 1984 (Box 25, Folder 233)
  - Books Received - Kaplan, Henry S. - "Hodgkin's Disease" [Grant-in-Aid], December 12, 1967-June 2, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 234)
  - Books Received - Kotro, Ronald F. - "Guide to the Archives and Manuscript Collection of College of Physicians of Philadelphia", April 17, 1977-December 12, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 235)
  - Books Received - Lewis, Irving J. - "The Sick Citadel: The American Academic Medical Center and the Public Interest", July 25, 1979-January 30, 1984 (Box 25, Folder 236)
  - Books Received - Lewis, Irving J. - "The Sick Citadel: The American Academic Medical Center and the Public Interest", July 25, 1979-January 30, 1984 (Box 25, Folder 237)
  - Books Received - Lipowski, Zbigniew J. - "Delirium: Acute Brain Failure in Man", February 4, 1974-September 10, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 238)
  - Books Received - Majno, Guido - "The History of the Wound", August 8, 1977-August 13, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 239)
  - Books Received - Mann, James - "A Casebook in Time Limited Psychotherapy" [Grant-in-Aid], February 2, 1970-June 18, 1979 (Box 26, Folder 240)
  - Books Received - Mann, James - "A Casebook in Time Limited Psychotherapy" [Grant-in-Aid], February 2, 1970-June 18, 1979 (Box 26, Folder 241)
  - Books Received - Mawardi, Betty H. - "The Physician and His Careers" [Grant-in-Aid], November 18, 1968-June 3, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 242)
  - Books Received - Miller, George E. - "Educational Science and Education in Medicine", August 24, 1976-June 3, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 243)
  - Books Received - Miller, George E. - "Educational Science and Education in Medicine", August 24, 1976-June 3, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 244)
  - Books Received - Moore-Ede, Martin C. - "The Clocks That Time Us: Anatomy and Physiology of the Mammalian Circadian Timing System", July 20, 1979-February 27, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 245)
  - Books Received - National Center for Faculty Development (Report on National Survey), February 16, 1978-May 10, 1979 (Box 26, Folder 246)
  - Books Received - Neisser, Arden - "The Other Side of Silence: Sign Language and the Deaf Community in America", February 23, 1979-February 23, 1984 (Box 26, Folder 247)
  - Books Received - Nicholas, Herbert G - "Washington Despatches 1941-1945", February 13, 1978-December 28, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 248)
  - Books Received - Orbach, Jack (Karl Spencer Lashley Lectures), December 14, 1978-May 17, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 249)
  - Books Received - Rhode Island Hospital - "Symptoms, Illness Behavior, and Help Seeking", May 7, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 250)
  - Books Received - Rhode Island Hospital - "Symptoms, Illness Behavior, and Help Seeking", May 7, 1981-January 4, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 251)
  - Books Received - Rhode Island Hospital - "Symptoms, Illness Behavior, and Help Seeking", May 7, 1981-January 4, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 252)
  - Books Received - Roemer, Milton I. - "Ambulatory Health Services in America: Past, Present and Future", June 2, 1977-September 1, 1981 (Box 27, Folder 253)
  - Books Received - Rubin, Ronald P. - "Calcium and the Sectory Process", March 18, 1980-March 7, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 254)
  - No Books Received - Abrams, Jonathan - "Physical Examination of the Cardiovascular System", September 12, 1978-October 14, 1981 (Box 27, Folder 255)
  - No Books Received - Ackerly, S. Spafford - "Oral History of the Child Guidance Movement in the United States", April 29, 1971-February 20, 1981 (Box 27, Folder 256)
  - No Books Received - Asper, Samuel P. - "Care Amidst Chaos", April 12, 1977-January 18, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 257)
  - No Books Received - Asper, Samuel P. - "Care Amidst Chaos", April 12, 1977-January 18, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 258)
  - No Books Received - Asper, Samuel P. - "Care Amidst Chaos", April 12, 1977-January 18, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 259)
  - No Books Received - Barger, A. Clifford - "Selected Diaries and Letters of Walter Bradford Cannon", October 24, 1977-January 11, 1982 (Box 27, Folder 260)
  - No Books Received - Blois, M. Scott - "The Nature of Medical Information", May 9, 1977-November 9, 1979 (Box 27, Folder 261)
  - No Books Received - Blois, M. Scott - "The Nature of Medical Information", November 29, 1979-December 18, 1979 (Box 28, Folder 262)
  - No Books Received - Cavalli-Sfforza, Luigi L. - "African Pygmies: An Investigation", January 6, 1972-November 30, 1982 (Box 28, Folder 263)
  - No Books Received - Chapman, Loring F. - "Behavioral Aspects of Human Brain Function", October 1, 1969-September 11, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 264)
  - No Books Received - Christie, Ronald V. - "Medical Education and the State" [Grant-in-Aid], December 26, 1967-December 22, 1970 (Box 28, Folder 265)
  - No Books Received - Christie, Ronald V. - "Medical Education and the State" [Grant-in-Aid], January 11, 1971-January 18, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 266)
  - No Books Received - Etzioni, Amitai - "New Definitions of Health and Medical Responsibility: A Critical Analysis", March 31, 1978-February 18, 1981 (Box 28, Folder 267)
  - No Books Received - Goodwin, Frederick and Kay R. Jamison - "Manic-Depressive Illness", June 20, 1980-July 21, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 268)
  - No Books Received - Hirsch, James G. - "Paul Ehrlich Biography", October 25, 1980-October 14, 1981 (Box 28, Folder 269)
  - No Books Received - Ingle, David - "Biological and Behavior Study of the Vertebrate Visual System", May 14, 1968-September 12, 1973 (Box 28, Folder 270)
  - No Books Received - Jackson, William V. - "Resources for Brazilian Studies at the Biblioteque Nationale", April 13, 1977-February 20, 1981 (Box 28, Folder 271)
  - No Books Received - Joynt, Robert - "History and Evolution of Neurological Principles", May 22, 1979-February 25, 1982 (Box 29, Folder 272)
  - No Books Received - Kark, Robert M. - "The Life and Times of Richard Bright", July 28, 1975-September 30, 1982 (Box 29, Folder 273)
  - No Books Received - Kark, Robert M. - "The Life and Times of Richard Bright", July 28, 1975-September 30, 1982 (Box 29, Folder 274)
  - No Books Received - Kass, Edward H. - "Thomas Hodgkin, M.D. (1798-1866): An Annotated Bibliography", March 29, 1967-March 30, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 275)
  - No Books Received - Knapp, Peter Hobart - "Psychoanalysis and Scientific Inquiry: The Future of an Illumination", October 26, 1972-March 6, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 276)
  - No Books Received - Koran, Lorrin M. - "Medical Disorders Presenting as Psychiatric Syndromes", September 23, 1971-June 7, 1978 (Box 29, Folder 277)
  - No Books Received - Lidz, Theodore - "Ethno-Psychiatry, Based on Experiences in Papua New Guinea", January 22, 1979-January 26, 1982 (Box 29, Folder 278)
  - No Books Received - Mason, Howard S. - "Functioning Biochemistry" [Grant-in-Aid], July 8, 1968-March 7, 1977 (Box 29, Folder 279)
  - No Books Received - Massachusetts General Hospital (Conference) [Grant-in-Aid], October 2, 1967-January 10, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 280)
  - No Books Received - Murray, Margaret R. - "Living Cell Neurobiology: Tissue Culture of the Vertebrate Nervous System", December 15, 1971-February 29, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 281)
  - No Books Received - Murray, Margaret R. - "Living Cell Neurobiology: Tissue Culture of the Vertebrate Nervous System", March 14, 1972-June 2, 1980 (Box 30, Folder 282)
  - No Books Received - Ripley, Herbert S. - "Suicidal Behavior", September 15, 1976-January 16, 1980 (Box 30, Folder 283)
  - No Books Received - Rosenberg, Charles - "Origins and Development of the American Hospital", May 29, 1974-September 12, 1980 (Box 30, Folder 284)
  - No Books Received - Rosenberg, Charles - "Origins and Development of the American Hospital", May 29, 1974-September 12, 1980 (Box 30, Folder 285)
  - No Books Received - Rothman, Stephen L. G. - "Computerized Tomography", December 21, 1977-October 15, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 286)
  - No Books Received - Shrand, Hyman - "Home Care for the Sick Child" [Grant-in-Aid], March 16, 1967-February 11, 1974 (Box 30, Folder 287)
  - No Books Received - Sonenberg, Martin and Norbert Swislocki - "Growth Hormone in Health and Disease" [Grant-in-Aid], May 28, 1970-March 31, 1971 (Box 30, Folder 288)
  - No Books Received - Stephens, F. Douglass - "Congenital Malformations of the Urinary Tract", August 20, 1979-December 6, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 289)
  - Miscellaneous - Consultants, April 2, 1981-July 1, 1981 (Box 30, Folder 290)
  - Miscellaneous - Correspondence, October 18, 1973-July 27, 1982 (Box 30, Folder 291)
  - Miscellaneous - Description, 1970-1979 (Box 30, Folder 292)
  - Miscellaneous - Directors' Meetings Reports, May 17, 1973-July 7, 1981 (Box 30, Folder 293)
  - Miscellaneous - Directors' Meetings Reports, May 17, 1973-July 7, 1981 (Box 30, Folder 294)
  - Miscellaneous - Evaluation, 1973-1974 (Box 31, Folder 295)
  - Miscellaneous - Evaluation (Daniel Zwick), March 10, 1980-July 10, 1981 (Box 31, Folder 296)
  - Miscellaneous - Grant-in-Aid, August 21, 1973-January 17, 1974 (Box 31, Folder 297)
  - Miscellaneous - Harvard University Press (Contract), July 1, 1975 (Box 31, Folder 298)
  - Miscellaneous - Harvard University Press (Contract Termination), July 9, 1981-November 4, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 299)
  - Miscellaneous - IRS Documents, February 8, 1973-July 7, 1982 (Box 31, Folder 300)
  - Miscellaneous - List of Publications, August 23, 1973-September 23, 1982 (Box 31, Folder 301)
  - Miscellaneous, January 17, 1974-April 1, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 302)
  - Miscellaneous - Renewal of Copyrights, September 16, 1947-February 1, 1978 (Box 31, Folder 303)
  - Miscellaneous - Report to Directors, November 8, 1973 (Box 31, Folder 304)
  - Miscellaneous - Report to Directors, November 8, 1973 (Box 31, Folder 305)
- Harvard Press Reports, 4
  The Commonwealth Fund had an agreement with the Harvard University Press to publish their books. The reports date from 1963 to 1982.
  - Analysis of Manufacturing Account, 1964-1976 (Box 32, Folder 306)
  - Analysis of Manufacturing Account, 1964-1976 (Box 32, Folder 307)
  - Analysis of Manufacturing Account, 1964-1976 (Box 32, Folder 308)
  - Analysis of Manufacturing Account, 1964-1976 (Box 32, Folder 309)
  - Analysis of Manufacturing Account, 1964-1976 (Box 32, Folder 310)
  - Analysis of Manufacturing Account, 1964-1976 (Box 32, Folder 311)
  - Analysis of Manufacturing Account, 1964-1976 (Box 32, Folder 312)
  - Analysis of Manufacturing Account, 1977-1982 (Box 33, Folder 313)
  - Analysis of Manufacturing Account, 1977-1982 (Box 33, Folder 314)
  - Analysis of Manufacturing Account, 1977-1982 (Box 33, Folder 315)
  - Fiscal Year Summaries, 1963-1974 (Box 33, Folder 316)
  - Sales Reports, June 1967-December 1968 (Box 33, Folder 317)
  - Sales Reports, June 1967-December 1968 (Box 33, Folder 318)
  - Status Reports, January 17, 1967-July 9, 1981 (Box 33, Folder 319)
  - Status Reports, January 17, 1967-July 9, 1981 (Box 33, Folder 320)
- Old Book Program - Authors Files, 5
  This subseries is arranged alphabetically by author.
  This subseries consists mostly of correspondence, grant-in-aid, financial papers, and pamphlets. The subseries is concerned with the writing and publishing of various authors' books. Nathan Talbot's manuscript of Functional Endocrinology is located in this subseries. The documents date from the late 1960s to the early 1980s.
  - Absolon, Karel B., August 29, 1978-July 17, 1984 (Box 33, Folder 321)